fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
W-What?
Where is this place?!
"Restricted Area"
"Do Not Enter"
This is the site of the second exam,
the 44th Training Field...
Also known as... the Forest of Death.
Forest of... Death?
Huh?
Is that supposed to be... a rock?
Moreover, on top of the grass?
Hey, Konohamaru!
What is it that you want?!
Just what I expect from the man I respect!
Good job on figuring it out!
Hey! Too much gunpowder used!
With an adult sexiness!
I'm Moegi of the senior class
at Kunoichi preschool!
I love factoring!
Udon!
The most brilliant Ninja in the village!
Konohamaru!
The three of us together are
the Konohamaru Gang!
Here we are!
What's going on you guys?
Hey, I'm about to take the
second exam for the Chunin Exam.
I have no time to be playing
around with you guys!
We didn't come to play around!
That's right!
We came here for an interview!
That's right...
Interview?
Yeah, we were put in charge to write
the feature article for the "Chunin Exam,"
for the academy's class newspaper.
So that's why we came to
interview you, leader...
Please cooperate with us.
Please.
But...
Hey, over there!
What are you doing?!
Konohamaru here is asking about
an interview for the class newspaper...
Oh, I forgot that Lord Hokage was
mentioning something like that.
Hey, hey...
All right, take a 10-minute break
starting now!
For those who will be interviewed,
resign yourselves and be courteous.
Hey, hey... What's this all about?
Big brother Naruto!
I'm depending on you.
All right!
In that case, I'll just show you
how attractive I am!
Must Watch!
Report before Entering the Forest of Death!
It's The Leaf's School Newspaper!
Chapter of
Character Introduction
Please introduce yourself.
Okay!
My name is Uzumaki Naruto!
A Ninja from Village Hidden
in the Leaves!
My hobby is to play pranks,
and I love ramen noodles,
I've just become a Genin but...
My dream is big, to become a Hokage!
And I'm going to surpass all
the Hokage from the past,
and make everybody in the town
acknowledge my existence.
I've been called a failure and such,
but I graduated splendidly and,
as a member of Group Seven
led by Kakashi-sensei,
I am dealing with
difficult missions every day!
Distance from the target?
5 meters.
I'm ready anytime.
In Group Seven, there is also
Sasuke and Sakura.
Since I'm really the only one that shows
great success,
you don't worry about the other two.
I got you!
Don't say such things.
Introduce them properly!
Is the target correct?
I know, I know.
The target confirmed.
For example, this guy's name is
Uchiha Sasuke
and he's a pretentious guy.
I heard that he's one of the last
remaining of the famous Uchiha clan,
but he really is a pitiful guy, like this...
Oh, this was when I transform but...
as long as you understand the greatness
of my Ninja skills that's all that matters.
Oh, and this is Haruno Sakura
who is in love with me.
You know, the more she denies it,
the more I'm convinced it's true.
She hardly tells me how
she really feels about me but,
her shyness makes her even cuter!
Is that true?
It really is true, true.
Who's in love with Naruto?!
Shannaro!
It was a lie after all!
I'm sorry...
Well, putting that aside,
three of us formed a team
and got through a bunch
of dangerous missions together.
Hey you...
What?
Oh, Missus!
I've gotten rid of all the weeds!
What?
What's wrong?
Those... those aren't weeds...
Huh?
Those are herbs I grew in my garden!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Somebody! Help...!
No!
Free Fall!
You idiot.
Trap Field Do Not Enter
Don't go over there!
Hey!
Please stop!
That fool...
Geez... All because he
stubbornly chose that big dog.
This is a dangerous mission?
It only looks like you're being clumsy, Naruto.
Yikes!
Well, there were times like that too.
Do it over.
Transform!
Oh, this was when I defeated
the Old Man Hokage.
This isn't going to make a good article.
Fine, then you show me how to do it.
Fine! My name is Konohamaru...
The grandson of the
town's chief Hokage.
Grandfather is the most important figure
in the Leaf Village
and is the third Hokage.
Those who succeed the Hokage name
is the top Ninja of the village.
Especially the 4th Hokage is a great hero
who protected the village
from the demon fox!
Hey, hey, hey wait!
You're only talking about other people!
I was just about to start on myself!
Besides, Bro, you talk too much
about yourself!
Of course, I am the star of the article,
other people don't matter!
You're right, Naruto...
Of course, you're going to forget
about me
when you graduate from the academy.
But you can introduce me for a bit...
Oh, yes, yes...
He is the first person in the town
who acknowledged me, Iruka-sensei...
He's a really nice person,
he always treats me to
ramen noodles at Ichiraku.
Am I just a nice person because
I treat you to ramen noodles?
Oh no... well... that's...
Don't laugh it off!
Big brother, next up,
I'm depending on you!
Oh, you're right!
Then, I guess I could talk
about Sasuke's stories of failures...
I've already heard that one.
Get more serious!
That Naruto...!
I bet he's just making up
stuff as he pleases...
Humph!
Who cares...
Chapter of Ninja Art
Well, now we'll have Haruno Sakura,
who is my senior as a Kunoichi,
teach us about Ninja Art.
Yes, I am the beautiful Kunoichi,
Haruno Sakura.
Beautiful?
What, you have any complaints?
Oh, no...
Transform!
Well first, Naruto's Ninjutsu...
Sexy Jutsu,
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Transform!
- Transform!
Harem Jutsu...
I call it, "Harem Jutsu"!
And something like this.
Hey!
It's his fault that he's late!
Dropping the blackboard eraser...
Next is the number one rookie, Sasuke,
who graduated as
the top student at the academy.
You won't get me by attacking
straight on.
The most popular one in class, he can
also fight Kakashi-sensei as an equal.
Sasuke is awesome!
Your Sasuke introduction
is taking too long.
Naruto, you're so noisy.
Stay quiet.
Horse!
Tiger!
Fire Style: Fire Ball Jutsu!
What?!
That's not a Jutsu Genin can use...
He couldn't have enough Chakra!
Demon Wind Shuriken
Windmill of Shadows.
Shuriken won't work on me.
I'll do it.
C-Could that be...?
Sharingan!
Is that, the Sharingan...?
If this is the same Kekkei Genkai
as Kakashi-sensei's...
he can read Bushy-Brow's Jutsu!
Genjutsu or Ninjutsu...
it's some kind of magic either way.
I'll reveal that!
Although you have seen Sasuke
using powerful Jutsu like
Fire Style: Fire Ball Jutsu,
Demon Wind Shuriken,
Windmill Shadow, and Sharingan,
the greatest of all is...
the sharp look of his eyes!
Any girl who has been stared
at with those eyes,
will fall in love with him!
Sasuke!
Look this way!
You're... annoying.
Well, that cold behavior is also
another attractive quality of Sasuke...
Next is our teacher,
Kakashi Hatake Sensei,
also known as
the Copy Ninja Kakashi.
He uses the Sharingan in his eye
to assess the enemy's technique
and copy over
a thousand Jutsu techniques.
But he's always late to meet people,
and whenever he has any time
he always reads this questionable book
called Make-Out Paradise,
and he always looks like he
doesn't really care about things...
Leaf Village Secret Finger Jutsu:
A Thousand Years of Death!
And the biggest mystery of all
is his face hidden under that mask!
I wonder what he really looks like...
Ninja Art, Summoning,
Earth Style: Fanged Pursuit Jutsu!
If you can't use your eyes or ears,
simply use your nose.
That's what happens when
you're closing your eyes in the midst of fog.
This is the Summoning Jutsu
specialized for pursuit.
On top of all that, why does he
have the Sharingan in his left eye
that is only passed on in the Uchiha clan?
One mystery after another when
it comes to this person,
so many things that I don't understand...
I should ask him next time
I have the chance.
Lightning Blade!
What the...?!
His hand is...
visibly overflowing with Chakra!
You are too dangerous.
Water Prison Jutsu.
Oh no!
Secret Jutsu.
Crystal Ice Mirrors!
Next up are the Ninjutsu of
the other Ninja besides us.
There's such a diverse collection of
Ninjutsu that I have no time to explain all...
Chapter of Rivals
Please, Sasuke,
whom I feel is like my future self,
take care of the next part.
Sure. After all, I have to be the one
to do something about it.
I knew that from the beginning.
Don't try so hard to look cool.
Sasuke, the snob.
Don't interfere.
Stay out of it, loser.
Annoying.
Shut up!
I hate the fact that only you stand out.
Nobody strong around you
shows any interest in you.
What the...?!
Just watch this.
Hey!
You there...
What's your name?
I'm Gaara of the desert.
I have an interest in you as well...
What's your name?
Uchiha Sasuke.
Hey, you there.
Identify yourself.
Dang it!
Again? It's always about Sasuke!
When asking someone his name,
give your own name first.
You, with the unpleasant look.
Wait a minute!
Why don't you fight with me here now?
I AM going to take out the Bushy-Brow!
The one I want to fight isn't you...
It's Uchiha.
Everybody says Sasuke, Sasuke!
It's annoying!
It's true!
Nobody thinks that you're
the main character leader!
That's not true, they're all just blind!
Huh... As usual you're just about
the talk and not the walk.
That's not true!
Leaf Whirlwind!
See, you are just about the talk.
Uhh... even Sakura is picking on me.
The students who gathered for
this Chunin Exam are all skilled,
and are the cream of the crop...
Nara Shikamaru, Akimichi Choji,
Yamanaka Ino,
Hyuga Hinata, Inuzuka Kiba & Akamaru,
and Aburame Shino...
You won't never be able to win
with the way you have been fighting.
You must understand that, right?
Y-Yeah! Of course!
You, too. Be careful not to let
your guard down
so you won't be defeated
by some lame guy!
Huh! Of course!
That's right...
We passed the first stage
of the Chunin Exam and
are heading to the location
of the second stage...
No matter what kind of adversity
may lie ahead,
we will not be afraid!
And we will pass the exam
to become a Chunin!
Because we... we...
have the greatest teamwork
that was formed by a strong bond!
Okay! Let's go!
Thank you so much for cooperating
with the interview!
– Thank you...
– Leader!
Do your best!
Yeah, leave it to me!
– Bye!
– See you!
– Do your best!
– Good luck!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
The 44th Training Field,
also known as the Forest of Death.
From here on it's a serious battle
between the Ninja,
anything could happen!
It's going down in earnest now!
This is getting interesting!
A life-risking survival game in the forest!
I will survive without fail!
Next time: "Second Exam Starts! Everyone Around Us is an Enemy!"
As for me, I'm going to kick butt again!